<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Media Player</string>
    <string name="Fragment_1_name">Songs</string>
    <string name="Fragment_2_name">Playlists</string>
    <string name="Fragment_3_name">Artists</string>
    <string name="Fragment_4_name">Store</string>

    <string name="Play_song_page_title">Play song</string>
    <string name="Purchase_song_page_title">Purchase song</string>

    <string name="tab_1_text">Songs</string>
    <string name="tab_2_text">Playlists</string>
    <string name="tab_3_text">Artists</string>
    <string name="tab_4_text">Store</string>

    <string name="tab_1_body">Here will appear a list with all songs; when the user clicks on one of the songs, a new activity will open which will play the selected song.
        \nPlease click on this text view.</string>
    <string name="tab_1_body_from_playlists">It will show a list with songs from the selected playlist; when the user clicks on one of the songs, a new activity will open
        which will play the selected song. \nPlease click on this text view.</string>
    <string name="tab_1_body_from_artists">It will show a list with songs sung by the selected artist; when the user clicks on one of the songs, a new activity will open
        which will play the selected song. \nPlease click on this text view.</string>
    <string name="tab_2_body">Here will appear a list of playlists. When the user clicks on one of the lists, will be directed to the page with Songs which are
        contained in the selected playlist.\nPlease click on this text view.</string>
    <string name="tab_3_body">Here will appear a list of artists. When the user clicks on one of the artists, will be directed to the page with Songs which are sung
        by the certain artist.\nPlease click on this text view.</string>
    <string name="tab_4_body">Here will appear a list of songs that can be purchased by the user. There will be more filters available (search by music genre, artist, song name).
        When the user selects the song that intents to purchase, a payment activity will open. Please click on this text view. </string>

    <string name="play_song_body">Here the user can see the song details and play it. \n\nWe will use the MediaPlayer class (https://developer.android.com/reference/android/media/MediaPlayer.html)
        in order to implement the play functionality.</string>
    <string name="purchase_song_body">Here the user can purchase the song with PayU money Gateway \n[public class PayUMoneyActivity extends AppCompatActivity]</string>

</resources>
